Finding Aid for Thompson Carriage and Paint Shop (Ypsilanti, Mich.) records, ca. 1842-ca. 1890
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Thompson Carriage and Paint Shop (Ypsilanti, Mich.) records ca. 1842-ca. 1890
Thompson Carriage and Paint Shop (Ypsilanti, Mich.)
1 linear foot (18 volumes)
86735 Bb 2
Ypsilanti, Michigan business; account books and daybooks.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group was the gift of B. C. Thompson of Ypsilanti, Michigan (donor no. 3007 ) and came to the library in 1953.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The record group is open to research.
Thompson Carriage and Paint Shop was a nineteenth century Ypsilanti, Michigan business.
The record group consists of account books and daybooks of the firm. Included is a record of log purchases, 1845-1853, and accounts of wheat purchased in 1842.
Subjects:
Business records.; Carriages and carts--Michigan--Ypsilanti.; Paint industry and trade--Michigan--Ypsilanti.; Thompson, Benjamin, b. 1805.; Thompson, O. E., b. 1838.; Washtenaw County (Mich.); Ypsilanti (Mich.)
- Account books and other financial records
  - Account book (O.E.) Thompson), undated (Box 1)
  - Account book of paint shop, ca. 1854-1861 (Box 1)
  - Account book (Benjamin Thompson), 1883-1890 (Box 1)
  - Account book of carriage repairs, 1860-1889 (Box 1)
  - Account and receipt book, ca. 1842-1865 (Box 1)
  - Account book, 1857-1861 (Box 1)
  - Account book, 1862-1864 (Box 1)
  - Account book, 1861-1868 (Box 1)
  - Account book, ca. 1868-1870 (Box 1)
  - Account book, ca. 1871-1886 (Box 1)
  - Account book, 1858-1861 (Box 1)
  - Account book, 1854-1859 (Box 1)
  - Daybook, 1862-1864 (Benjamin Thompson and Rubin Gould) (Box 1)
  - Account book, 1853-1858 (Box 1)
  - Account book, 1845-1852 (Box 1)
  - Account and receipt book, 1842-1871 (Box 1)
  - Account and correspondence book, 1866-1869 (Box 1)
  - Account book, 1883-1891 (Mrs. B.N. Thompson ?) (Box 1)